Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Wright, Maurice (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus (1972 A.B. Music. Magna cum laude; musician and composer
- Wright, Patricia (Box 109)
- Wright, Patricia (Box 145)
- Wu, Lawrence (Box 109)
- Wuenscher, James Edward (Box 109)
- Wylie, Donald P. (Box 60)
- Wylie, Donald P. (Box 145)
- Wylie, Donald P. (Box 157)
- Wylie, Hilda (Box 60)
- Wyngaarden, James (Box 109)
- Wyngaarden, James (Box 145)
- Wyngaarden, James (Box 157)
- Wyngaarden, James B. (Box 60)
- Wynkoop, Rodney Alan (Box 109)
- Wynkoop, Rodney Alan (Box 145)
- Yaggy, Duncan (Box 109)
- Aharoni, Yair (Box 157)
- Yancy, Sam (Box 60)
- Yancy, Sam (Box 145)
- Yancy, William S. (Box 109)
- Yandle, David O. (Box 60)
- Yandle, David O. (Box 145)
- Yang, Dennis T. (Box 109)
- Yang, Weitao (Box 109)
- Yates, Warren Grice (Box 60)
- Yoder, Barbara A. (Box 109)
- Yoh, Harold L., Jr., Trustee (Box 118)
- Yohe, William P. (Box 110)
- Yoho, James G. (Box 60)
- Yoho, James G. (Box 110)
- Yoho, James G. (Box 145)
- Yoho, James G. (Box 157)
- York, Brantley (Box 60)
- York, Brantley (Box 110)
- York, Brantley (Box 145)
- York, Brantley (Box 157)
- You, Kwan-sa (Box 60)
- Young, Betty Irene (Box 110)
- Young, Cabell, Jr. (Box 60)
- Young, Charles R. (Box 110)
- Young, David B. (Box 60)
- Young, Edward Hudson (Box 60)
- Young, Edward Hudson (Box 145)
- Young, Edward Hudson (Box 157)
- Young, Franklin W. (Box 110)
- Young, Franklin W. (Box 145)
- Young, Helen R. (Box 110)
- Young, James S. (Box 60)
- Young, James S. (Box 110)
- Young, James S. (Box 145)
- Young, Paul (Box 60)
- Young, R.T. (Box 145)
- Young, R.T. (Box 60)
- Young, Stephen L. (Box 110)
- Young, W. Glenn (Box 110)
- Young, W. Glenn (Box 145)
- Younger, Ben (Box 110)
- Younger, John G. (Box 110)
- Younger, John G. (Box 145)
- Younger, Kenneth Glen, Trustee 1985-1991, Trustee (Box 118)
- Younts, Worth D. (Box 110)
- Yuan, Fan (Box 110)
- Zalutsky, Michael Rod (Box 110)
- Zankel, Harry T. (Box 60)
- Zankel, Harry T. (Box 145)
- Zarkin, Gary (Box 110)
- Zegler, Richard (Box 110)
- Zeigler, Lynn (Box 60)
- Zeigler, Lynn (Box 145)
- Zener, Karl E. (Box 110)
- Zener, Karl E. (Box 145)
- Zener, Karl Edward (Box 60)
- Zernov, Nicholas (Box 60)
- Zernov, Nicholas (Box 145)
- Zernov, Nicholas (Box 157)
- Zheng, Fangyang (Box 110)
- Zhou, Xueguang (Box 110)
- Ziegler, Lyman (Box 60)
- Zimmerman, Maj. Gen. Matthew (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus (Divinity 1965); First Black graduate from Duke Divinity School; Veterans' Affairs National Chaplain Center
- Zinna, Rosario F. (Box 110)
- Zipkin, Paul H. (Box 110)
- Zizioulas, John D. (Box 60)
- Zmijewski, Chester M. (Box 110)
- Zsolnay, Adam (Box 60)
- Zukowski, Halina A. (Box 60)
- Zung, William Wen-Kwai (Box 110)
- Zung, William Wen-Kwai (Box 145)